She is the star of the play,
and she is my girlfriend.
이 연극의 주인공은
바로 내 여자친구지
I get to have sex with the star
of the play!
이 여주인공과
사랑을 나눴다고
-People can hear you.
-I know!
사람들이 듣잖아
아무렴!
She looks great, doesn't she?
캐시 근사하지?
- 반갑소
- 어서 와요
That is one good-looking man.
저 남자도 끝내주는데?
Is it just me, or can you actually
see his abs through his overcoat?
저 친구 코트 위로
튀어나온 게 배 근육 맞니?
So you been doing this long?
이런 일한 지 오래됐나?
No. You're my first.
Put the money on the table.
아뇨, 당신이 처음이에요
돈은 테이블 위에 두세요
그렇지
That's nice.
좋았어
Dude!
저런!
-ls that an expensive blouse?
-lf you want it to be.
이 블라우스 비싼 건가?
좋을 대로 생각해요
Here's your girlfriend's button.
네 애인 단추다
The One with Rachel's Crush
Do you still have your old blouses
and dresses from high school?
너 혹시 고등학교 때 입던
블라우스나 드레스 있니?
Yeah, I think I have some around
here somewhere. Why?
어디 몇 벌 있을 거야, 왜?
임신복이 너무 비싸더라
Maternity clothes are so expensive.
Rach, I made a pile of your stuff.
If you could just...
레이첼, 네 짐은
이쪽에 뒀으니까...
...throw your purses at it.
여기다 가방 던져
Bloomingdale's eliminated
my department.
우리 부서가 없어졌어
어머! 그럼 해고된 거야?
Are you out of a job?
No, but they stuck me in Personal
Shopping, which is a huge step down.
개인쇼핑 담당으로 밀렸어
보기 좋게 좌천당한 거지
개인쇼핑이 뭔데?
What is that?
Where you walk around with rich people
and tell them what to buy?
콧대 높은 부자들 따라다니며
비싼 물건 구경시켜 주는 거?
맞아
That sounds great!
신나겠다!
안녕?
동작 그만
We switched apartments. You can't eat
our food. That gravy train has ended.
집 바꿨으니까 우리 음식에
손대지 마, 이제 국물도 없어
There's gravy?
국물 있어?
큰 집이 생겼으면
알아서 손님들 대접해
If you have the big apartment, you
have to deal with people coming over.
너희 냉장고나 채워 놔
이제 거긴 너희 집이야
That fridge has to be stocked.
That's your apartment now.
-What are you doing?
-I think I left a doughnut up here.
뭐해?
여기 도넛을 뒀는데
- 얘들아
- 그래
How was Kathy's play?
캐시 연극 어땠어?
캐시가 반쯤 벗은 채 근사한
남자랑 부둥켜안고 구르더라
Kathy gets half-naked and simulates sex
with a real good-looking guy.
마치 내 악몽을 보는 듯했어
32달러나 주고서
It's like somebody wrote down
my worst nightmare...
...and then charged me $32 to see it.
That's a good idea for a business.
그거 괜찮은 사업이다
I'm totally screwed. They're gonna be
hot and heavy on stage every night...
돌아가시겠군, 저녁마다
무대에서 저럴 거 아냐
...then they'll go to their cast parties,
and he's gonna try to undermine me.
배우들끼리 파티라도 하면
날 안주 삼아 씹어대겠지?
He'll be like, "Where's your boyfriend?
What's his name? Chester?"
'남자친구는 뭐해?
체스터라고 했나?'
She'll go, "It's Chandler."
He'll go, "Whatever!"
'아니, 챈들러야' 그러면
'뭐든 간에, 하하하하하! '
That is a good trick.
우린 그렇게 놀아
All right, look.
What am I going to do?
이제 난 어떡하냐
그 사람들은 배우야
그게 직업이라고
They're actors.
They're there to do a job.
같이 공연한다고
사귀는 건 아냐
It doesn't mean they're
gonna get together.
Just because it happened with
Susan Sarandon and Tim Robbins...
수잔 서랜든과 팀 로빈스는
특수한 케이스라 이거야
...doesn't mean it's gonna
happen with them.
알렉 볼드윈이랑
킴 베이싱어도 있다
Alec Baldwin and Kim Basinger.
- 탐 크루즈랑 니콜 키드만
- 맞아
Tom Cruise and Nicole Kidman.
멜 깁슨하고
클린트 이스트우드
Mel Gibson and Clint Eastwood.
They're not a couple.
그 사람들은 커플 아냐
I get the game now.
아! 그런 게임이구나
All these people were in movies together.
It's much different with plays.
다 영화배우잖아
연극하고는 달라
You were in acting class
together, and she slept with you.
넌 연기학교 다니다
캐시하고 잤잖아
Acting class is a lot more
like a movie than a play.
연기학교는 연극보다
영화 쪽에 가깝지
When they were doing it on stage,
was it really hot?
하나만 물어보자
두 사람 무대에서 뜨거웠니?
아무렴
Oh, yeah.
그렇다면 걱정할 거 없어
So you're fine.
The rule is when two actors
are actually doing it off-stage...
거기엔 규칙이 있거든
배우들이 실제로 사귀면
...then all the sexual tension
between them is gone.
둘의 성적 긴장감이 사라져
As long as it's hot on stage,
you got nothing to worry about.
무대에서 화끈하다면
신경 쓸 거 없다니까
When the heat goes away,
that's when you're in trouble.
무대에서 시들하면
진짜로 심각하지
Really?
정말?
You guys have been to every play I've been
in. Have I ever had chemistry on stage?
너희들 내 연극 다 봤지?
내가 진짜처럼 하던?
- 아니
- 거봐!
-No.
-No!
Are you gonna go see
the play with me tonight?
오늘 함께 극장에 갈 거지?
좀 그렇다, 네 애인하고 다른
남자의 정사를 점검하다니...
I don't know how comfortable I am going
to see how hot the sex is between them.
-I know, but
-No, I'm there.
- 그건 알지만...
- 당연히 가야지
- 안녕
- 어서 와
-Want some pancakes?
-You made pancakes?
팬케이크 먹을래?
- 팬케이크를 만들었어?
- 그럼, 접시 잡아
Grab a plate.
No, no. Stay right there.
아냐, 거기 있어
Getting closer.
점점 가까워진다
Don't worry...
걱정 마, 시리얼에
머핀과 와플, 또...
...we also have cereals,
muffins, waffles and...
...jams, jellies and marmalades,
which I'm sure are the same thing.
잼, 젤리, 마멀레이드도 있어
내가 보기엔 다 똑같지만
Please eat, because Joey
opened everything.
제발 먹어줘
조이가 다 따버렸어
We're watching the game here Saturday
night, if people wanna come over.
토요일 저녁에 TV로
게임 볼 거니까 모두 와
좋지
난 우리 집에서 보자고
할 생각이었는데
I was thinking about having people over.
Yeah? Who's playing?
그래? 무슨 시합인데?
The players.
운동시합
Somebody seems to be missing
being the hostess.
누구는 안주인 역할이
무척 그리운가 보다
Please. It's a relief, is what
it is, is what it is.
천만에, 속편해서
날아갈 것 같네요
됐다
피비, 접시 잡아!
Pheebs, stick out your plate.
모니카, 나 때려치울래
Monica, I'm quitting.
I just helped an 81-year-old woman put on
a thong, and she didn't even buy it.
81살 할머니한테 실 팬티를
입혔는데 안 사고 가버렸어
I'm quitting.
정말 그만둘 거야
당장 사표 낼래
I'm talking to my boss right now.
진심이야, 그럼, 맞아, 물론
메시지 확인하면 전화해
Yes, I am. Yes, I am.
Okay, bye. Call me when you
get this message.
월섬 씨, 드릴 말씀이 있어요
Mr. Waltham?
I really need to talk to you.
In a moment, please.
I'm in the middle of a task.
지금 바쁘니까
나중에 하세요
And you have a customer.
손님 오셨어요
어서 오세요
Hi.
조슈아라고 합니다
Hi, I'm Joshua.
네, 레이첼 그린이에요
뭘 도와드릴까요, 조슈아?
I'm Rachel Greene.
What could I do for you, Joshua?
I need a whole new wardrobe. My wife
Well, my ex-wife
옷을 전부 새로 사야 합니다
아내가... 실은 전처지만...
I'm so sorry.
어머나, 이를 어째
전처가 내 옷을 전부 태워서
이거하고 치마 하나 건졌어요
Anyway, she burned all of my clothes.
I got away with this suit
and what turned out to be a skirt.
Well, at least that's a great suit.
어쨌든 멋진 양복이네요
치마 입고 이걸 세탁소에
맡기러 갈 땐 처참했죠
It wasn't much fun dropping
it off at the dry cleaners in the skirt.
I need everything down to underwear.
If you're willing, I'm all yours.
속옷까지 전부 필요합니다
아가씨한테 모두 일임하죠
Okay.
좋아요
You needed to speak to me?
레이첼, 할말이 있다구요?
No, no, that wasn't me.
아뇨, 제가 아닌데요?
그럼 시작해볼까요?
제 속옷부터 보여드리죠
We should get started.
Let me show you my underwear.
The selection of underwear
that we carry.
저희가 엄선한 속옷들 말예요
I'm sorry.
아니, 이쪽이에요
-It's this way.
-This way? Sorry.
이쪽? 죄송합니다
I'm right. Right? There was
no chemistry between them.
내 말이 맞지?
두 사람 진짜 무덤덤했어
Before, they had heat.
Now, there's no heat.
전엔 화끈했는데 이젠 아냐
You know what this means.
Joey told us what this means.
조이가 가르쳐줬잖아
이게 무슨 뜻이겠어
멋대로 비약하지 마
그렇게 싱겁진 않았어
Let's not jump to any conclusions.
There was some sexual chemistry.
두 사람 사촌 같더라
Come on.
It was like cousins having sex.
온다, 제발 입 꽉 다물고
평상시 너처럼만 굴지 마
Here she comes. Don't say a word.
Just be cool. Don't be, you know, you.
Hey, you guys!
- 왔어요?
- 안녕
Thank you so much for coming again.
또 와줘서 고마워요
오늘 괜찮았어?
-Did you like it tonight?
-Absolutely.
그럼요
Wasn't Nick funny when
he couldn't get his match lit?
닉이 성냥을 못 켰잖아
It's a good play, isn't it?
- 좋은 작품이지?
- 음...
I loved the play.
You were great.
맘에 들었어
자기도 훌륭했고
닉도... 이하동문!
And Nick, ditto.
Clearly, you're having sex with him.
확실히 그 놈이랑 잤더구만
Okay....
저기...
Clearly, I'm having sex with him?
그 사람이랑 뭘 어째?
다 알아, 두 사람 연기
전혀 실감나지 않았어
It was so obvious.
There was no chemistry between you two.
You're accusing me of cheating on you,
and you're insulting my performance?
그러니까 내가 자기를 속이고
연기까지 형편없었다?
I can see how this could happen. You're up
there every night naked, touching, kissing.
모를 줄 알아? 두 사람 매일
무대에서 벌거벗고 뒹굴잖아
연기야, 내 직업이라고
Acting. Chandler, this is my job.
I'm playing a part in a play.
How can you not trust me?
역할에 충실할 뿐이야
어떻게 날 의심해?
You can understand,
given how we started.
우리가 어떻게
시작했는지 생각해봐
세상에, 자기 입에서
그런 말이 나오다니
I can't believe you're
throwing that in my face.
That is what happened.
I don't even see you denying this.
사실이 아니면
아니라고 해봐
I'll tell you what, Chandler.
You call me when you grow up.
잘 들어, 챈들러
철들면 그때 전화해
Don't expect that to happen
any time soon!
한참 기다려야 될 걸?
I have the best job
in the entire world!
이렇게 멋진 직업이 있다니
근사한 남자손님이 왔는데
The most adorable guy came over,
and I got to dress him up all day!
종일 그 사람
옷 갈아 입혔어
Rachel has a new doll!
새 인형이 생겼구나
정말 인형이라면 레이첼
인형이랑 뽀뽀시킬 텐데
I wish he was a doll. I'd get a Rachel
doll and bump them together...
...and make kissing noises.
예전엔 몰랐는데 그 이름은
또 얼마나 멋져? 조슈아!
He's got the most beautiful name.
I never realized. Joshua.
오, 조쉬... 우아!
Joshua.
Joshua. Josh.
조슈아! 조쉬!
어, 여보세요?
Hello?
Hi.
왜 그러시와요?
What do I smell?
무슨 냄새지?
I don't know. It smells good.
글쎄, 냄새 좋은데?
오븐에서 방금 구워낸
따끈따끈한 쿠키랍니다
Fresh cookies! Hot from the oven.
자, 어서 드세요
Please, have some.
- 맛있겠다
- 심심해서 한번 만들어봤어
I've been fiddling around here,
making delicious treats for everyone.
- 플레이보이 최신호?
- 그냥 사봤어
The new Playboy.
Just something I picked up.
Cookies and porn?
You're the best mom ever!
쿠키에 포르노잡지까지?
세상 최고의 엄마다!
What?
왜, 뭔데?
조슈아가 V-넥을 두고 한
말인데 너흰 들어도 몰라
It's just something Joshua said about
V-necks, but you had to be there.
How does Jason look in a V-neck?
제이슨은 V-넥 잘 어울려?
조슈아야
-It's Joshua.
-Whatever.
오, 뭐가 됐든
Wait. Wait. This isn't takeout!
잠깐, 들고 가는 거 아냐!
-Hate to eat and run.
-No, wait. Please, don't go!
- 먹고 튀기는 싫은데
- 안돼, 가지 마
너희들 포르노도 있어
I've got porn for you too.
I don't need it.
난 필요 없는데?
People are supposed to want
to hang out here.
여기서 놀아야지
Why? What is the big deal?
너 왜 그래?
I'm the hostess.
안주인은 나니까!
Not those guys.
I'm always the hostess.
쟤들이 아니라
내가 안주인이야
Even when I was little, the girls
brought their dollies to my tea party.
난 옛날에 소꿉놀이할 때도
최고의 빈 찻잔을 냈던 몸이야
I served the best air.
언제는 더 큰 집에서
놀아야 한다면서?
Why'd you make a big thing out of everyone
hanging out in the big apartment?
'Cause they took our apartment.
I wanted to punish them.
우리 집을 뺏었으니까
혼 좀 나보라고 그랬지
하지만 이 정도면
고통은 충분할 거야
I'm done now. They've suffered enough.
If you wanted to punish them, you should
have just made them hang out here.
진짜 벌을 주려면
여기서 놀라고 해야지
그렇다
That is true.
알았어, 여기 정리 끝나면
저 집보다 열 배는 좋아져
This place is gonna be 10 times
better than that place.
Are we gonna
trash their place?
그럼 저 집 망가뜨릴까?
There's steps!
우라질!
Slut!
걸레!
You'll all be very happy to hear
that Kathy is sleeping with that guy!
기쁜 소식을 알려주지
캐시가 그 놈이랑 잤어
-What?
-You were right?
- 뭐?
- 네 짐작이 맞았어?
I confronted her,
and she didn't deny it.
직접 대놓고 물었는데
부인을 못하더라
I don't live here!
우리 집도 아니네!
챈들러...
Wait, are you sure?
잠깐, 확실한 거야?
I may be drunk,
but I know what she said.
취하긴 했지만 캐시가
뭐라고 했는지는 알아
Then I went over
to Beefsteak Chewley's....
난 '비프스테이크
출리'에 가서...
-Beefsteak Charlie's?
-Yes!
- 비프스테이크 찰리?
- 맞아!
You and l
have always been like:
역시 너하고 난...
- 너무했다
- 이런 일이 있냐
Man, I am so sorry.
The bartender taught me
a trick, though.
바텐더한테 배운 거야
I don't remember it.
까먹었네
웁스!
- 내가 좀 도와줘?
- 아니, 됐어
-Do you need help with that?
-I got it.
난 이래서 청소기 안 써
I just feel bad. I never vacuum.
- 나 왔어
- 어서 와
I was with Joshua for an hour today,
and he has not asked me out.
한 시간이나 함께 있었는데
데이트신청을 안 하더라
김 팍 샌다
-Just so frustrating.
-Why don't you ask him out?
네가 먼저 신청해
Totally. That's such a turn-on.
맞아, 그거 엄청
자극적이거든
Really? It doesn't seem desperate?
정말? 너무 싸 보이잖아
That's the turn-on.
그래서 자극적이지
얼마 전에 이혼해서
몸을 사리는 거야
He just got a divorce. Right?
He's probably really nervous around women.
네가 선수를 쳐
Maybe you just need to
make the first move.
남자한테 데이트신청
해본 적 없는데?
-I've never asked a guy out before.
-You've never asked a guy out?
한 번도 안 해봤어?
No. Have you?
- 그래, 넌 해봤어?
- 수천 번!
Thousands of times!
내세울 건 없다, 그치?
That doesn't make me
sound too good, does it?
I don't even know
how I would go about it.
어떻게 하는지 모르는 걸?
내 경우엔 여자를 위아래로
훑어본 후 이렇게 말하지
What I do is, I look a woman
up and down, and I say...
..."Hey. How you doing?"
'헤이... 안녕하쇼'
어우, 관둬라
Oh, please!
Hey. How you doing?
헤이! 안녕하쇼...
You know what? I'm gonna do that.
I'm gonna call him up and ask him out.
그래, 전화를 걸자
만나자고 할 거야
I can do that, ask him out.
할 수 있어
못할 게 뭐야
"How you doing?"
안녕하쇼...
조슈아, 블루밍데일의
레이첼 그린이에요
Hi, Joshua.
It's Rachel Greene from Bloomingdale's.
네, 여쭤볼 게 있는데...
I was just wondering if you...?
If you...
혹시...
오늘 지갑 놓고 가셨나요?
...Ieft your wallet
at the store today?
매장에서 지갑을 주웠는데...
We found a wallet, and we
The license? That is a good idea.
면허증이라...
좋은 생각이네요
어디 보자
면허증에는...
Well, let's see.
This license belongs to...
...belongs to a Mr. Pheebs.
이게 누구냐
미스터... 피브스!
네, 괜한 폐를 끼쳤군요
내일 뵐게요, 그럼
So sorry to bother you at home.
I'll see you tomorrow. Bye.
-You've done that a thousand times?
-I've never done that.
- 이걸 수천 번 해봤어?
- 너처럼은 안 했다
I just got so nervous that he'd say no.
거절할까 봐
말을 못 꺼내겠어
You gotta give him something
he can't say no to, like...
거절 못하게 만들어야지
가령... 닉스 게임 티켓
...Knicks tickets. Invite him to a Knicks
game. You're guaranteed he'll say yes.
닉스 게임에 초대하면
당연히 승낙하겠지
-Really? You think that'll work?
-Absolutely. And if not, can I go?
정말 효과가 있을까?
물론, 안 먹히면
표는 내가 가진다?
What the heck is that?
무슨 소리지?
Did she call?
캐시 전화는?
아니, 안 왔어
No. Sorry.
Maybe I should call her.
내가 전화해야겠다
안돼, 잊어버려
네가 뭐가 아쉬워서
Forget her, man. You don't need her.
He's right.
What she did was unforgivable.
맞아, 용서 못할 일이야
하지만 혹시 내가
오해한 거라면?
Well, yeah, but, you know,
what if I was wrong?
How might you be wrong?
오해라니
What if she didn't actually
sleep with the guy?
그 녀석이랑 정말
잔 게 아니면?
캐시가 정확히 뭐라고 했니?
Tell me she told you this.
She didn't have to tell me.
I saw the play. There was no heat.
무슨 말이 필요해
심드렁한 연기였어
-Back me up.
-That's all you're basing this on?
- 좀 도와줘, 로스
- 그걸 보고 단정했냐?
그건 도움이 안돼!
That's not backing me up!
Look, you said,
"With the offstage and the heat"
그랬잖아, 실제로 사귀면
연기는 무덤덤해지고...
그건 이론일 뿐이지
엉터리 이론이 얼마나 많은데
That was just a theory. There's a lot
of theories that didn't pan out:
Lone gunman, communism, geometry.
케네디 단독암살설
공산주의, 기하학...
Oh, my God!
잘 빠졌다!
"Would you like to go
to a basketball game with?"
농구경기 어때요?
아냐...
"It's funny, basketball,
because I happen to have tickets"
우연히 농구경기
티켓이 생겼는데...
"Who likes the Knick?"
닉스 팀 좋죠?
What do you think?
어때요?
보자, 미혼여성으로서
애인 없는 처녀로서
Well, as a single woman,
who is available...
...I think you look great.
너무 근사하군요
그래요?
네, 아주 멋져요
Oh, yeah. You look great.
네, 잘 어울려요
This looks great.
맘에 들어요?
So you like it?
I do. I love it.
In fact, I think I'll wear it home.
네, 아주 좋군요
입고 갈까 봐요
-Great.
-Thank you so much for all your help.
- 좋아요!
- 도와줘서 정말 고마워요
Well, I guess this is it.
- 이제 다 끝났군요
- 네에...
Thanks.
고마워요
Maybe I'll see you in the spring
for the bathing suits.
봄에 수영복이나 보러 오죠
지금 봐도 되는데?
You don't want to do that now?
That's okay.
됐어요
I'll see you around sometime.
다음에 또 보죠
Basketball!
농구는요?
Sorry?
네?
저기...
I have two tickets to the
Knicks game if you're interested...
감사의 뜻으로 닉스 게임
티켓 두 장을 마련했어요
...just as a thank-you for this week.
- 와! 그거 좋죠!
- 그래요?
That would be great!
-Really?
-That would be fantastic!
이럴 수가, 조카 녀석이
닉스 팀이라면 미치는데
My nephew is crazy about the Knicks!
This is fantastic.
Thank you so much, Rachel.
이렇게 고마울 데가 있나
- 안녕하세요
- 반갑습니다
Good morning.
- 왔어?
- 그래
I just wanted to come over
to say that I'm sorry.
사과하려고 왔어
I acted like the biggest idiot
in the world.
내가 바보등신이었어
자기가 화낸 거 이해해
I can completely understand
why you were so upset.
I really wish you'd called me.
전화하지 그랬어
나도 전화하고 싶었어
어찌 보면 잘된 일이야
Yeah, I know. I wish I had too.
I think this is a good thing.
처음으로 다퉜으니
좀더 가까워질 거야
We've had our first fight,
and now we can move on.
I know for me, but
자기도 알겠지만 난...
Nick's pants?
닉의 바지야?
그래
그렇군
두 번째 싸움은
정말 커지겠어!
I think our second fight
is going to be a big one!
다음번엔 어떻게 말하라고?
-For next time, what do you say?
-"l have an extra ticket."
티켓 한 장이 남았다
두 장이 아니라 한 장
"An extra ticket."
Not "two tickets."
The first time you asked a guy out
he turned you down?
첫 번째 데이트신청에서
물을 먹은 거야?
He didn't turn me down.
He's at the game.
그게 아냐, 나만 경기장에
못 간 것뿐이라고
I got the date.
I'm just not on it.
Okay, it's ready.
자, 다 됐어
어서 와
-Come on.
-What's ready?
다 되다니
Just come.
일단 와봐
Oh, my God!
세상에!
- 얘...
- 굉장하다!
This is beautiful!
Did you work for two days straight?
이틀 밤을 새운 거야?
Pretty much.
그런 셈이지
What do you think of the floor?
바닥 어때?
I don't know.
Looks the same.
글쎄, 똑같은데?
You used to have carpet.
전엔 카펫이었잖아
Oh, yeah.
그렇지!
I made snacks.
먹을 것도 있어
Please, just hang out.
편하게 놀아
난 눈 좀 붙일게
I'm just gonna rest my eyes
for just a little bit.
우리 나중에 다시 올까?
Do you want us to come back later?
No, no, no. Stay.
Just keep talking.
아냐, 그냥 있어
대화들 나누라고
I'm always the hostess.
난 영원한 안주인이야
이봐
How'd it go?
- 잘됐어?
- 어때?
-She wasn't sleeping with him.
-Good!
놈이랑 잔 건 아니래
다행이다
She is now.
근데 지금은 자
-What are you saying?
-I'm saying that she is a devil woman.
무슨 소리야
무슨 소리냐면...
막돼먹은 여자야!
You think you know a person, then they
turn around and sleep with Nick.
그 사이에 닉이랑 붙어먹다니
Nick and his rock-hard pecs
and his giant man-nipples.
사내자식이 가슴팍만
크고 땡땡하면 다야?
I hate him.
And I hate her.
망할 자식!
망할 계집애!
I don't hate her. I love her.
This is all my fault.
아니, 난 캐시를 사랑해
다 내 잘못이지
How? How is it your fault?
그게 왜 네 잘못이야
내가 전화를 안 했으니까
I should have called.
If I had called her, she never
would have gone out with Nick.
싸운 뒤에 전화만 했어도
닉과 한 침대에 들진 않았어
They wouldn't have ended up in bed.
I threw her at his man-nipples!
내가 그 가슴팍에 안겨준 거야
This is not your fault.
네 잘못이 아냐, 한번 다퉜다고
딴 사람이랑 자는 게 말이 되니?
Your fight does not
justify her sleeping with someone.
Well, if she thought
they were on a break....
끝났다고 생각하면
그럴 수도 있지
Rachel, one of your customers seems to
have left his billfold, a Joshua Burgen.
레이첼? 고객이 지갑을
놓고 가신 모양이에요
조슈아 버겐?
Really?
정말요?
-Will you call him?
-Yes, I will. Absolutely.
레이첼이 연락하겠어요?
네, 그럼요
물론이죠
Hello, Rachel.
안녕, 레이첼
Hi, Joshua.
네, 조슈아
-I left my wallet here on purpose.
-Really?
일부러 지갑을 놓고 갔소
정말이에요?
Yes. I just wanted to see you again.
당신을 또 만나고 싶어서
I'm glad.
저도 기뻐요
Rachel, I'd like to say
something to you.
레이첼, 당신한테 할말이 있소
Yes?
뭐죠?
"How you doing?"
안녕하쇼...